To honour the JVM settings for this build a single-use Daemon process will be forked. For more on this, please refer to https://docs.gradle.org/8.13/userguide/gradle_daemon.html#sec:disabling_the_daemon in the Gradle documentation.
Daemon will be stopped at the end of the build 

> Configure project :
WARNING: The option setting 'android.defaults.buildfeatures.buildconfig=true' is deprecated.
The current default is 'false'.
It will be removed in version 10.0 of the Android Gradle plugin.
To keep using this feature, add the following to your module-level build.gradle files:
    android.buildFeatures.buildConfig = true
or from Android Studio, click: `Refactor` > `Migrate BuildConfig to Gradle Build Files`.
WARNING: BuildType 'debug' is both debuggable and has 'isMinifyEnabled' set to true.
All code optimizations and obfuscation are disabled for debuggable builds.

[Incubating] Problems report is available at: file:///D:/Projects/BlueReader/build/reports/problems/problems-report.html
